

Ankit Pahwa

E-mail: ankit.pahwa315@gmail.com Phone: 9992300388

Address: House No: 186, Vpo: Damkora, Teh: Tohana, Dist:

Fatehabad

OBJECTIVE

Master of computer application having 5 years of experience in iOS App Development. My objective is to work in an innovative environment, where I can enhance and make best use of my skills for the betterment of organization in the direction of gaining certain professional growth.

TECHNICAL ACQAINTANCE

Operating Systems / Platforms: Mac OS-X, iOS

Programming Languages: Swift, Basic of SwiftUi

OOPS Concept

Databases: CoreData, Firebase

Payments: Paypal, Braintree, Paytm

Work experience

ToXSL Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Jan 2016 — Dec2017

Software Engineer iOS Development

Igniva Infotech Pvt. Ltd. Feb2018 — 27May2019

Software Engineer iOS Development

Chetu India Pvt Ltd. Jun2019 — 15Jun2020

Software Engineer iOS Development

PROJECT UNDERTAKEN

Project Title: Al-fathia [Live]

Technology: Swift, Firebase

id1199635059?mt=8/الفاتحة-AppLink :- https://itunes.apple.com/in/app/al-fatiha/الفاتحة

Project Title: BabbleApp [Live]

Technology: Swift, GooglePlaces, LinkPreview

AppLink :- https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/babbleapp/id1368444203?ls=1&mt=8

Ankit Pahwa

Project Title: RavNav [Live]

Technology: Swift, chat, UBER integration

AppLink :- https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/ravnav/id1314208126?ls=1&mt=8

Project Title: BUUS [Live]

Technology: Swift, Stripe, CoreData

AppLink :- https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/buus/id1409544911?ls=1&mt=8

Project Title: MJBUDDY [Live]

Technology: Swift, Google Maps

AppLink :- https://itunes.apple.com/in/app/mj-buddy/id1305064705?mt=8

Education

MCA 2013 — 2016

JMIT(Radaur)

Stream: Computer Science & Engg.

BCA 2010 — 2013

IG Govt College

Stream: Computer Science.

Personal Details

Father's Name: Satish Kumar Pahwa

Date of Birth: 13 Jan 1992

Languages Known: Hindi, English

Ankit Pahwa 2